琼安好不好？
So how was Joan?
跟她分手了
Broke up with her.
为什么？
Oh,why?
别告诉我 因为鼻孔太大？
Don't tell me. Because of the big nostril thing?
真的超大！
They were huge!
她打喷嚏时 会有蝙蝠飞出来
When she sneezed,bats flew out of them.
没那么大
They were not that huge.
当她仰起头时 我可以看到她的脑子
I'm telling you,she leaned back,I could see her brain.
你到底要拒绝多少好女孩…
How many women will you reject...
只是因为非常肤浅的事情？
...over superficial,insignificant things
慢着，我必须帮钱德说话
Hold it. I gotta side with Chandler on this one.
我刚搬到这里时 与一个女孩交往
When I first moved here,I went out with this girl.
非常热情，很会接吻…
Really hot. Great kisser...
但是她的喉结非常大粒！
...but she had the biggest Adam's apple.
真是让我受不了
Drove me nuts.
你说还是我说？ 我来好了
-You or me? -I got it.
乔伊，女人没有喉结
Joey,women don't have Adam's apples.
你们是在骗我，对不对？
You guys are messing with me,right?
对，我们在骗你！
Yeah. We are!
真好笑 我差点上当了
That's a good one. For a second there,I was like,whoa!
The One Where Heckles Dies
六人行 第2季 第03集 哈克先生之死
你与哪个女友分手 是因为正当的理由？
You name one woman that you broke up with for an actual real reason.
莫琳罗西洛
Maureen Rasillo.
因为她不讨厌音乐家雅尼 这不是个正当的理由
Because she doesn't hate Yanni is not a real reason.
嗨，哈克先生
Hello,Mr. Heckles.
你们又做了
You're doing it again.
我们什么都没做
We're not doing anything.
你们脚步声太响 吓到了我的鸟儿
You're stomping. It's disturbing my birds.
你没有养鸟
You don't have birds.
我可以养鸟
I could have birds.
我们会小声一点
We'll try to keep it down.
谢谢
Thank you.
我要回去继续我的晚宴了
I'm going to rejoin my dinner party.
好，再见
All right,bye-bye.
对了，珍妮丝
Okay,Janice.
珍妮丝可以证明 我并没有乱挑剔
Give me Janice. That wasn't about being picky.
我们同意你与珍妮丝分手
We'll give you Janice.
但我蛮想珍妮丝的
I miss Janice,though.
嗨，钱德宾！
Hello,Chandler Bing!
喔，我的天！
Oh,my God!
喔，钱德！
Oh,Chandler!
现在就要！
Now! Now!
对了
That's it.
对了！快一点！
There! Faster!
别用扫把了！ 我们没有制造噪音！
Stop with the broom! We're not making noise!
我们赢了
We won.
我们胜利了！
We did it!
哈克先生！
Mr. Heckles!
怎么发生的？ 他大概在扫地
-How did this happen? -He was sweeping.
他们发现他抓着一把扫把
They found a broom in his hand.
真糟糕 我知道
-That's terrible. -I know.
昨天我也在扫地
I was sweeping yesterday.
搞不好也会一命呜呼
It could've been me.
扫地，真是没想到
Sweeping. You never know.
世事难料
Never know.
很微弱 但我还可以感觉他在大楼里
It's very faint,but I can still sense him in the building.
进入光芒中，哈克先生！
Go into the light,Mr. Heckles!
好了，菲比
Okay,Phoebe.
对不起 有时候他们需要帮助
I'm sorry,but sometimes they need help.
又来了
Here we go.
很好，嘲笑我吧
That's fine,go ahead and scoff.
我不相信很多事情…
There are a lot of things I don't believe in...
但这不表示就不是真的
... but that doesn't mean they're not true.
譬如什么事？
Such as?
像是麦田怪圈或百慕达三角 或进化论
Like crop circles or the Bermuda Triangle or evolution.
你不相信进化论？
What,you don't believe in evolution?
不真的相信
Not really.
你不相信进化论？
You don't believe in evolution?
我不知道，只是…
I don't know. It's just,you know....
猴子，达尔文，很好的故事 我只是觉得有点太简单
Monkeys,Darwin,it's a nice story. I just think it's a little too easy.
太简单？太…
"Too easy"? Too
这个星球上的一切生物 经过数千万年…
The process of every living thing on this planet evolving...
从单细胞微生物进化而成 而你说太简单？
...over millions of years from single-celled organisms is "too easy"?
对，我不买账
Yeah,I just don't buy it.
对不起 进化论不是信不信由你，菲比
Excuse me. Evolution is not for you to buy,Phoebe.
进化论是科学事实 就像我们呼吸的空气…
Evolution is scientific fact,like the air we breathe...
就像地心引力
...Iike gravity.
别跟我提起地心引力
Don't get me started on gravity.
你不相信地心引力？
You don't believe in gravity?
倒不是相不相信的问题
Well,it's not so much that,you know,I don't believe in it.
最近我感觉到…
Lately I get the feeling that...
我不是被吸住，而是被压着
...I'm not so much being pulled down as I am being pushed.
被压着…
Pushed.
那一定是伊萨克・牛顿，他出来尿尿了
It's lsaac Newton and he's pissed.
快点菲比，跳到天花板上去
Quick, Pheebs, hop on the ceiling.
她在这，那里还有另一个
There she is. And over there,that's the other one.
这是伯弟杜尔 哈克的律师
This is Mr. Buddy Doyle,Heckles' attorney.
他想跟你们谈谈
He'd like to talk to you.
有何贵干？
What can we do for you?
好了，孩子们 事情是这样的
All right,kids,here's the deal.
根据我客户的遗嘱…
According my client's will...
他要把他所有财产…
... he wants to leave all his earthly possessions...
都留给楼上吵闹的女孩们
...to "the noisy girls in the apartment above mine."
他的家人呢？
What about his family?
他没有家人
He didn't have any.
好，让我们看看有多少钱
Okay,so let's talk money.
好，没有半毛钱
All right,there was none.
现在，我们来签字
Now,let's talk signing.
你是一号吵闹女孩 你是二号吵闹女孩
You be noisy girl number one. You be noisy girl number two.
我真不相信 我们一直以为他讨厌我们
I can't believe that this whole time we thought he hated us.
真是不可思议 我们能如此感动其他人…
Isn't it amazing how much you can touch someone's life...
而自己却不知道？
...without even knowing it?
看看这个猪窝？！
Would you look at this dump?
他痛恨我们！ 这是他最终的报复！
He hated us! This was his final revenge!
我从来没看过这么多废物！
I've never seen so much crap!
我觉得这间公寓 侮辱了废物的美名
Actually,I think this apartment sullies the good name of crap.
看看这个
Check this out.
这个能给我吗？
Can I have this?
你怎么能不相信进化论？
How can you not believe in evolution?
我不知道，就是不相信 看看这条怪衬衫！
I don't know,just don't. Look at this funky shirt!
菲比 我整个成年都在研究进化论
Pheebs,I've studied evolution my entire adult life.
我们从世界各地搜集化石
And we've collected fossils from all over the world...
能够证明不同物种的进化论
...that actually show the evolution of different species.
可以真正看到它们…
I mean,you can literally see them...
透过时间进化
...evolving through time.
真的？可以看得到？
Really? You can actually see it?
千真万确！在美国 中国，非洲，全世界！
You bet! In the U.S.,China,Africa,all over!
这我不知道
See,I didn't know that.
这就是吧
Well,there you go.
问题是 谁把化石放在那里？为什么？
So now the real question is,who put those fossils there and why?
看看这个！ 我的痛苦之书
Look at this! My Big Book of Grievances.
嘿，这是我！
Hey,there's me!
四月十七日，噪音过度…
"April 1 7th,excessive noise...
意大利佬带了女伴回家
... Italian guy comes home with a date."
你也在里面
You're in here too.
四月十八日，噪音过度…
"April 1 8th,excessive noise...
意大利佬的同性恋室友 带了干洗衣服回家
... Italian guy's gay roommate brings home dry cleaning."
真是太好了
Well,that's excellent.
看看这盏灯
Look at this lamp.
真是够俗了 我们一定要带回去！
Is this tacky or what? We have to have this.
我们的好台灯够多了
I think we have enough regular lamps.
什么？好啦，我又不是…
What? Come on,it's not like...
要这个美女时钟或什么的
... I'm asking for this girlie clock or anything.
但我觉得这个也很酷
Which,by the way,I also think is really cool.
听着，它与我的东西都不搭配
Look,it doesn't go with any of my stuff.
那么我的东西呢？
Well,what about my stuff?
你没有任何东西
You don't have any stuff.
这个将成为我的东西
It will be the start of my stuff.
不
No.
你还是认为那是你的公寓 对不对？
You still think of it as your apartment,don't you?
对，你是这么想
Yes,you do.
你把它想成是你的公寓 我只是租了个房间
You think of it as your apartment and I just rent a room.
你支支吾吾的时候 我会为我的新台灯找个地方放
While you "mmm" on that,I'll go find a place for my new lamp.
菲比 看我玩这些小玩具
Okay,Pheebs. See how I'm making these little toys move?
可对立的拇指！
Opposable thumbs!
没有进化论 怎么发展出可对立的拇指？
Without evolution,how do you explain opposable thumbs?
也许外星主宰需要这样的拇指才能够驾驶空间飞船
Maybe the Overlords needed them to steer their spacecrafts.
请说你是在开玩笑
Tell me you're joking.
能不能说你相信进化论 而我不相信？
Look,can't we say that you believe in something and I don't?
不行，菲比 就像数学，1加1等于2
No, Pheebs, we can't. Because it's like math. One plus one equals two.
我不能让你认为等于3或者等于4或者等于黄颜色
I can't let you think that it might equal three or four or yellow.
为什么不行？这有什么关系？
Why not?. No, what is that all about?.
为什么非得每个人都同意你？
What is this obsessive need to make everybody agree with you?
你知道吗？
You know what?
我想你也许应该把罗斯放到显微镜下面好好看看
I think maybe it's time you put Ross under the microscope.
我耳朵有没有流血？
Is there blood coming out of my ears?
看看这个 哈克的高中同学录
Check it out. Heckles' high-school yearbook.
他看起来好正常！
He looks so normal!
甚至有点可爱
He's even kind of cute.
“哈克 你上科学课总是让我捧腹大笑”
"Heckles,you crack me up in science class.
“你是全校最有趣的学生”
You're the funniest kid in school."
最有趣？哈克？ 上面是这样写的
-Funniest? Heckles? -That's what it says.
哈克被选为班上的活宝 我也是
Heckles was voted class clown,and so was l.
他说得对！ 听听那个噪音？
He was right! Would you listen to that?
的确是很吵闹
I'd call that excessive.
什么？
What?
哈克在乐队演奏竖笛 我也是
Heckles played clarinet in band,and I played clarinet.
他参加模型俱乐部 我也…
He was in the scale modeler's club and I was
虽然我的学校没有俱乐部 但我觉得模型很酷
There was no club,but I sure thought they were cool.
所以你们两个都是书呆子
So? You were both dorks.
没什么值得大惊小怪
Big deal.
我觉得很怪，哈克与我…
I just think it's weird,you know? Heckles and me
哈克与我，我…
Heckles and me. Me
我与哈克
Me and Heckles.
喂，别吵好不好！
Hey,would you knock it off!
你整晚都在这里？
Have you been here all night?
看看这个
Look at this.
哈克交往过的女人照片
Pictures of all the women Heckles went out with.
看看他在上面写的 “薇安，太高大”
Look what he wrote on them. "Vivian,too tall."
“玛姬，牙龈太大”
"Madge,big gums."
“太大声”
"Too loud."
“太聪明” “吃东西发出声音”
"Too smart." "Makes noise when she eats."
这就是我
This is me.
这就是我的作法
This is what I do.
我会像他一样孤独终老
I'm gonna end up alone,just like he did.
哈克是个神经病
Heckles was a nut case.
我们的人生道路方向一样
Our trains are on the same track.
我比他晚了30年 但终点都是一样
I'm coming up 30 years behind him,but the stops are all the same.
愁苦城…
Bitter Town...
孤独镇，隐士村！
...Alone-ville,Hermit Junction!
我们应该离开这里
You know what we gotta do? Get you out of here.
我请你吃早餐
I'll buy you breakfast.
要是我一直找不到伴侣怎么办？ 或更糟的，我已经找到了…
What if I never find somebody? Or worse,what if I found her...
但我却因为她把“或许”说成“厚许”就甩了她？
... but I dumped her because she pronounces it,"supposably"?
钱德，好啦 你会找到对象的
Chandler,come on,you're gonna find somebody.
你怎么知道？
How do you know that? How?
我不知道 我只是想帮你下台
I don't know. I'm just trying to help you out.
你们将来都会结婚…
You guys will all get married...
我会孤独一人
...and I'll end up alone.
你能不能答应我一件事？
Will you promise me something?
你结婚后 过节时能不能请我去玩？
When you're married,will you invite me over for holidays?
我不知道我们会怎么样
I don't know what we'll be doing.
要是我们到她的父母那里过节呢？
I mean,what if we're over at her folks' place?
我了解
Yeah,I understand.
你可以过来看超级杯
You can come over and watch the Super Bowl.
每一年都来，怎么样？
Every year,all right?
我不要像这样子下场！
You know what? I'm not gonna end up like this.
待会见，兄弟
I'll see you,man.
“厚许”…
"Supposably."
“厚许”！
Supposably!
他们去动物园了吗？
Did they go to the zoo?
“厚许”吧…
Supposably.
嗨，是我
Hi. It's me.
我的天！
Oh,my God!
珍妮丝？你打给珍妮丝？
Janice? You called Janice?
是的，珍妮丝
Yes. Janice.
有什么难懂的？
Why is that difficult to comprehend?
你还记得珍妮丝吧？
You remember Janice,right?
是啊，她很聪明，很漂亮 而且很关心我
Yes. She was smart,she was pretty and she honestly cared about me.
珍妮丝是我的最后一个希望
Janice is my last chance to have somebody.
喔，天啊！
Oh,my God!
她真是胖了不少
Jeez,look how fat she got.
嗨，大家都在这里！ 嗨，珍妮丝
-Hey,it's everybody! -Hi,Janice.
珍妮丝，你…
Janice,you're....
是的，我有了
Yes,I am.
是不是… 是不是你的？
-ls it? -ls it yours?
没那么好的事，钱德宾！
You wish,Chandler Bing!
我已经是已婚女士了
You are looking at a married lady now.
恭喜
Congratulations.
亲爱的，真抱歉，我不可能等你一辈子
Sweetie,I'm sorry.I couldn't wait for you forever.
你不能在电话上告诉我吗？
You couldn't tell me on the phone?
要我错过看到你的表情？ 才不要！
And what? Miss the expression on your face? Oh,no!
珍妮丝喜欢乐子！
Janice likes to have her fun!
你知道我们很久没玩什么吗？
You know what we haven't played in a while?
藏起台灯
Hide the lamp.
莫妮卡，算了吧
Monica,let it go.
你知道我对贝类过敏吗？
Did you know I'm allergic to shellfish?
那么你将必须吃掉其他的台灯
Then you'll just have to eat the other lamps.
可怕的科学家来了
It's scary scientist man.
菲比，这些就是了
Okay,Phoebe,this is it.
在这个手提箱中 我带来了真正的科学证据
In this briefcase I carry actual scientific facts.
可算是整个提箱的证据
A briefcase of facts,if you will.
其中有些化石超过2亿年
Some of these fossils are over 200 million years old.
我要先告诉你 我并不否定进化论
Before you even start,I'm not denying evolution.
进化论只是可能性之一
It's just one of the possibilities.
进化论是唯一的可能
It's the only possibility.
罗斯 你能不能稍稍敞开心胸？
Ross,could you just open your mind,like,this much?
以前最聪明的人 不也相信地球是平的？
Didn't the brightest minds in the world believe the Earth was flat?
五十年前，科学家认为 原子是最微小的事物
And up till 50 years ago,you thought the atom was the smallest thing...
后来科学家击碎了原子 于是产生了各种玩意…
...until you split it open and this whole mess of crap came out.
难道你是如此自大…
Are you telling me that you are so unbelievably arrogant...
无法承认有一点点的可能…
...that you can't admit that there's a teeny,tiny possibility...
你们科学家也许会犯错？
...that you could be wrong about this?
是有一点点…
There might be...
一点点…
...a teeny...
非常一点点…
...tiny...
…的可能
... possibility.
我真不相信你屈服了
I can't believe you caved.
你放弃了你的整个信仰！
You just abandoned your whole belief system!
以前我虽然不同意你 但我至少尊敬你
Before,I didn't agree with you,but at least I respected you.
但是…
But....
明天你要怎么继续研究？
How are you gonna go into work tomorrow?
你要如何面对其他科学家？
How are you going to face the other science guys?
你要如何面对你自己？
How are you going to face yourself?
真好玩，有谁饿了？
That was fun. So who's hungry?
我饿了
I am.
我也是 我去拿外套
Me too. Let me just get my coat.
怎么了？
What happened?
这是意外，我发誓
It was an accident,I swear.
我正在穿外套 台灯就破了
I was putting on my jacket and the thing and the lamp and it broke.
拜托，莫妮卡！ 你痛恨我的台灯！
Oh,please,Monica! You've always hated my lamp!
突然间 它就奇迹似地破了？
And now all of a sudden,it's just magically,it's just broken?
菲比，告诉她
Phoebe,tell her?
我没看到 因为我正在穿外套
I didn't see it,because I was putting on my jacket.
但我想要相信你
But I want to believe you.
嗨，钱德 莫妮卡打破了我的贝壳台灯
Hey,Chandler. Monica just broke my seashell lamp.
真好
Neat.
我会死得孤苦伶仃！
I'm gonna die alone!
好，算你赢
Okay,you win.
钱德，你不会死得孤苦伶仃
Chandler,you are not gonna die alone.
本来珍妮丝是我的安全保障
Janice was my safety net,okay?
现在我必须去养一条蛇了
And now I have to get a snake.
为什么？
Why is that?
如果我会成为孤独老人 我需要养个东西
If I'm gonna be an old,lonely man,I'm gonna need a thing.
有个依靠
You know,a hook.
就像地铁上那个吃自己脸的人
Like that guy on the subway who eats his own face.
我会成为 “养蛇的疯老头”
So I figure I'll be "Crazy Man With A Snake."
养蛇疯子
Crazy Snake Man.
然后我会养更多蛇 当成我的子女
Then I'll get more snakes,call them my babies.
小孩都不敢经过我的门口！
Kids will run past my place!
他们会叫道： 养蛇疯子要来抓人了！
"Run away from Crazy Snake Man," they'll shout!
你必须想开一点
You've got to get over this.
你不会孤苦伶仃
You won't end up alone.
我当然会
Of course I will.
我甩掉了所有笨得愿意跟我交往的女孩
I reject anyone who's crazy enough to actually go out with me...
然后我抱怨找不到好女孩
...and then I bitch that there aren't any great women out there.
我们所交往的男人…
You have just described...
就跟你所描述的一样
...virtually every man that we've ever gone out with.
你没什么问题 你只是个平常人
You are not a freak. You're a guy.
她说得对，你们做的都一样
She's right.You all do it.
有个人不再看我是因为他的猫不喜欢我
This one guy stopped seeing me because his cat didn't like me.
或者因为我在脊背穿刺的时候睡着
Or because I fell asleep during Spinal Tap,
你在脊背穿刺的时候睡着？
You fell asleep during Spinal Tap?.
泰迪不再看你是因为你太胖了
Teddy, who stopped seeing you because you were too fat.
他说他没空是因为要看球赛
He said he didn't have time for me because of the play.
这就是我说的
That's what I said.
我的意思是，你与其他人没什么不同
My point being,you are no different than the rest.
等一下，等一下 他是不一样
Wait a minute,wait a minute. Yes,he is.
你其实很不一样
You are totally different.
很糟糕吗？
In a bad way?
不，亲爱的，是很好的不一样
No,honey,in a wonderful way.
现在你知道你要什么了
You know what you want now.
大多数男人根本不知道
Most guys don't even have a clue.
你准备好接受风险了 准备好接受伤害，与人亲近
You're ready to take risks,be vulnerable and intimate with someone.
你不会孤苦伶仃的
You're not gonna end up alone.
你打电话给珍妮丝 这证明你希望与人厮守终生！
You called Janice. That's how much you wanted to be with someone!
你已经改变了！ 你不一样了！
-You've made it! -You're there!
你准备好做出承诺了！
You are ready to make a commitment!
但是我自己却不知道！
Don't know about that!
你拿了什么？
What you got there?
不是你的东西 而你想要打破？
Something else that's not yours that you can break?
我知道你喜欢这个 我也要你收下它
I know you like this and I want you to have it.
在我们公寓会很好看
It'll look good in our apartment.
谢谢
Thank you.
没关系
That's fine.
你们会很高兴知道 明天晚上我有约会
You'll all be pleased to know that I have a date tomorrow night.
我的同事爱莉森 人很不错
This woman Allison from work. She is great.
她又漂亮又聪明 我一直…
She's pretty,she's smart. And I've been...
没有约她出来 因为她有一个…
... holding off asking her out in the past,because she has a...
不寻常的大头！
... unusually large head.
但我不要让这种事情阻止我
But I'm not going to let that stuff hang me up anymore.
看看我，我成熟了
Look at me. I'm growing.
你不要同学录对吧？
You can't recycle yearbooks,can you?
那个给我
I'll take that.
你要他的同学录？
You want his yearbook?
有人说了他的好话 应该留下来
Some people said nice things about him. Somebody should have it.
这真的很奇怪
Gosh,this is so weird.
他整个生命都在这公寓度过 现在人去楼空
His whole life was in this apartment and now it's gone.
我想我们应该为 哈克先生默哀一会儿
I think it would be nice if we just took a few moments for Mr. Heckles.
他是个麻烦人物 但他是个人
He was kind of a pain. He was,but he was a person.
你们全都会下地狱
You're all going to hell.
其实没有那么大！
It's really not that big!
你要拿那个走？ 没错
-Taking that with you,huh? -Oh,yeah.
你来吗？
You coming?
等一下
In a second.
再见，哈克先生
Goodbye,Mr. Heckles.
我们会安静点
We'll try to keep it down.
我完全学非所用
My major was useless.
报纸上什么时候看的到 “征求哲学家”？
How often do you look in the classifieds and see "Philosopher Wanted"?
对啊
Sure.
天啊，那真是个大头！
My God,that's a big head!
在办公室看起来没这么大 也许是因为灯光
It didn't look this big in the office. Maybe it's the lighting.
我的头在公司 一定像个高尔夫球那么小
My head must look like a golf ball at work.
不要想了 快列出你喜欢她的五件事
Don't get hung up on it. Quick! List five things you like about her.
笑容很美，衣着高雅
Nice smile,good dresser.
大头，大头，还是大头！
Big head,big head,big head!